{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How many pets do I currently have?",
      "options": {
        "1": "1",
        "2": "2",
        "3": "3",
        "4": "0"
      },
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favourite colour?",
      "options": {
        "1": "Green",
        "2": "Red",
        "3": "Orange",
        "4": "Purple"
      },
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "When's my birthday ðŸ˜ž",
      "options": {
        "1": "May 20th",
        "2": "May 21st",
        "3": "May 14th",
        "4": "May 30th"
      },
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Including this one, how many gifts have I given you?",
      "options": {
        "1": "5",
        "2": "2",
        "3": "3",
        "4": "6"
      },
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favourite meal?",
      "options": {
        "1": "Sopa de puchero",
        "2": "Milanesa napolitana",
        "3": "Fideos",
        "4": "Puchero"
      },
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many siblings do I have?",
      "options": {
        "1": "5",
        "2": "2",
        "3": "4",
        "4": "3"
      },
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What superpower would I choose?",
      "options": {
        "1": "To be able to see the future",
        "2": "To be able to travel into the past",
        "3": "To be able to fly",
        "4": "Super strength"
      },
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song was played on your previous birthday gift?",
      "options": {
        "1": "Amiga mÃ­a",
        "2": "Perfecta",
        "3": "Mi persona favorita",
        "4": "TÃº"
      },
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favourite season?",
      "options": {
        "1": "Spring",
        "2": "Summer",
        "3": "Fall",
        "4": "Winter"
      },
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "How many languages do I speak?",
      "options": {
        "1": "3",
        "2": "2",
        "3": "4",
        "4": "1"
      },
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you enjoying this gift?",
      "options": {
        "1": "Yes!",
        "2": "NO",
        "3": "Not sure..",
        "4": "Meh"
      },
      "correct": -1
    }
  ]
}
